<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="AnyEditTools"
      label="AnyEditTools"
      version="2.2.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Andrei Loskutov"
      plugin="de.loskutov.anyedit.AnyEditTools"
      image="loskutov32.gif">

   <description url="http://andrei.gmxhome.de/anyedit/index.html">
      Adds useful context menu actions to text files and editors - Open file, type under
      cursor, Convert tabs to spaces, case, html, base64, unicode, Compare/Replace with
      clipboard or external files etc. AnyEdit can remove trailing whitespace and/or
      convert tabs-spaces on save and contributes Import/Export working sets wizards.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://andrei.gmxhome.de/anyedit/copyright.html">
      Copyright (C)2002 - 2008 by Andrei Loskutov &lt;Loskutov@gmx.de&gt;.
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://andrei.gmxhome.de/anyedit/copyright.html">
      Copyright (C)2002 - 2008 by Andrei Loskutov &lt;Loskutov@gmx.de&gt;.
All rights reserved.
Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTORS ``AS
IS&apos;&apos; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHOR OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT
LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF
THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Andrei Loskutov plugins site" url="http://andrei.gmxhome.de/eclipse/"/>
      <discovery label="Andrei Loskutov plugins site" url="http://andrei.gmxhome.de/eclipse/"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime" version="3.3.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.console"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.debug.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.compare"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.net"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.expressions"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="de.loskutov.anyedit.AnyEditTools"
         download-size="400"
         install-size="400"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
